Now listen, yo!
People put your guns up
First I'll run dat
Run around and shoot them
Brand new sound, yes still survival
Here comes the sound boy, live in this world
Intelligence, strength, and luck are swirling, flow
My swelled mind is candid
One punch to Banner in Savannah
An easy knockout, bam bam bam
One time for your mind, live through this
Around the world
It haunts me, the pain of the past
Around the noble god are borrowed things
When the seed that's sown flowers, whose is it
Live and fire the arrow of faith, more more more
There is no peace where you're going
Come on, stand up, don't give up the fight
Now, yes, this instant, die die die
Big shooter, living fast, blazing
Beat you up, cut it open, break
Shot shooter, he lived fast, crazy
Adjust your sights at point-blank range, break
Big shooter, living fast, blazing
Beat you up, cut it open, break
Shot shooter, he lived fast, crazy
Adjust your sights at point-blank range, break
（リポーター）さて 今朝も また
あの“高校生失踪事件”の続報です
This morning, once again, we have a follow-up
on those missing high school boys.
（歩(あゆむ)）じゃ いってきます！
Okay, see you later!
（加藤(かとう)）おう！
（歩）ハハッ…
Yeah.
The two boys suddenly disappeared
in the subway.
（リポーター）地下鉄で こつ然と
姿を消した２人の男子高校生
その後 当番組でも―
Since then, we've tried to investigate the incident
from many different angles on this show,
さまざまな角度から
検証してみましたが―
but the identities of the missing high school
students have yet to be determined.
行方不明となっている高校生の
身元は いまだ判明しておりません
（加藤の叔母）まったく
最近の高校生ときた日にゃ―
Honestly! When it comes to
high school students these days,
they're a bunch of good-for-nothings!
ろくでもない
They up and disappear, causing a big fuss.
勝手に行方くらまして
世間を騒がして
未成年のくせに
何さまのつもりかねえ
Where do a couple of minors get off
doing something like that?
It's simply dreadful!
あ～ ヤダ ヤダ
However, we believe that tracing the sales of
the plastic umbrella and the adult magazine
（リポーター）
しかし このビニール傘と―
ヘアヌード写真集の
販売ルートを調べることにより…
Scene of the Incident
Station
However, we believe that tracing the sales of
the plastic umbrella and the adult magazine
Scene of the Incident
Station
will turn up some promising leads.
Scene of the Incident
Station
I certainly hope you aren't up to anything
strange outside of this house.
Will turn up some promising leads.
（叔母）あんたも外で 妙なこと
してるんじゃないだろうね？
I certainly hope you aren't up to anything
strange outside of this house.
Will turn up some promising leads.
I certainly hope you aren't up to anything
strange outside of this house.
I won't have you doing anything that
would bring shame to this household.
この家(うち)に
恥かかせるようなことしたら―
承知しないよ！
Well...
（加藤）あの…
メシいいですか？
May we eat now?
What?
（叔母）はぁ？ 冗談じゃないよ
Don't make me laugh!
Don't you understand the reason
why I made you sit there like that?
そこに そうやって
座らされてる意味が―
分かんないのかい？
Yesterday this stupid brat
tracked mud on the carpet!
このバカガキがね
昨日 カーペットに泥つけたんだよ
I had a terrible time getting it out.
取るの大変だったんだ！
なにが食事だい！
So why should you get any food?
（加藤）ちょっと靴下が
汚れていただけでしょう！
His socks were only a little dirty!
Talking back to me, are you?
口答えするのかい　居候のくせに…
You're nothing but a couple of freeloaders!
何だい その目は！ 手を離しな！
What are you looking at me like that for?
Let go of my hand!
お… 俺は いいです
だけど 歩には朝メシを…
You can do what you want with me,
but let Ayumu have some breakfast.
（叔母）離せって言ってるでしょう
こら 離せ！
Didn't I tell you to let go?! Come on, let go!
And... I'm begging you.
（加藤）それと お願いですから
これ以上 歩に―
Please don't raise your hand
to Ayumu any more. Please!
手を上げないでください
お願いします
That hurt!
痛いじゃないか！
If you don't like the way I do things here,
then you can get out!
文句があるなら
出てってくれていいんだよ　ああ？
We believe we can expect even more
surprising developments.
（リポーター）
今後 更なる 意外な展開が
待ち受けているものと思われます
（歩）うん
それでね また兄ちゃんがさ…
So my brother said he'd make me a new one.
Ayumu, your brother's no good at all.
（加藤）
歩 兄ちゃん ダメダメだよな
Ayumu, your brother's no good at all.
We're After You
（計(けい)）
なんだよ　もっと こっち来いよな
What's with you? Come closer.
Okay, is this all right?
（岸本(きしもと)）じゃ これ いい？
（計）はぁ？ そんなのが朝メシ？
What? That's your breakfast?
だって…
（計）ダメだって
But...
No, you've gotta at least eat some bread.
せめて
パンぐらい ちゃんと食わないと
Don't worry. It's pet food. This'll do.
（岸本）いいの
ペットのエサだもん　これくらいで
（計）そういう言い方すんなよな…
You don't have to say it like that.
But you don't have to...
いいのに
（計）“いい”って？
Don't worry.
But you don't have to...
Do you have the money?
お金あるの？
（計）はぁ？
If you run out of money, I'll be in trouble too.
玄野(くろの)君のお金なくなっちゃったら
私だって困るし
な… なんか それリアルだけど
そこまで言わなくても…
That's a somewhat sobering remark,
but you didn't have to go that far.
平気だから 俺
（岸本）そう？
It's no sweat.
Oh, really?
（女性）あの… 日出台(ひのでだい)は
あっちでいいんでしょうか？
Excuse me... Is that the way to Hinodedai?
Which platform do I go to?
（女性）
ホームは どっちに行けば…
て… てめえ
It's you...
（女性）
これ みんな タダで差し上げます
I'll let you have this for free.
In exchange, tell me the right platform.
その代わり
ホーム教えてくださいな
Where do I go?
どこに行けば…
（計）ウッ… ウウ…
（岸本）ちょっと 玄野君？
（計）ウワーッ！
Hey, Kurono!
どうしたの？
What's the matter?
Here it is!
あった！
Hey, that's...
あっ それ…
（計）やべえぞ　岸本 もうすぐだ
This is NOT good.
Kishimoto, it's almost time!
えっ 何が？
Time for what?
（計）あのばばあだって！
That old bag!
When we were called to that apartment
the other day,
俺 この間 あのマンションに
呼ばれたときも―
あいつに話しかけられたんだ
（岸本）えっ？
she came up and talked to me!
（計）
もうすぐガンツの呼び出しがある
Soon we'll get a call from Gantz.
と… とにかく
いつ呼ばれてもいいように―
Anyway, we have to put these on, so we'll be
ready no matter when we get called.
こいつだけは着とかないとさ…
（岸本）あっ…
Kurono...
玄野君
（計）あっ…
お… お尻 結構 白いんだね
You've got quite a pale behind.
うっ… えっと… そう？
Oh... Really?
Grandma! I wanna do it!
（亮太(りょうた)）おばあちゃん 僕やりたい
Really? You think you can do it?
（カヨ）そうかい？ できるかい？
Uh-huh, uh-huh! Gimme the money!
（亮太）
できる できる！ お金貸して
There you go.
（お金を入れる音）
（亮太）ねえ ねえ おばあちゃん
Hey, Grandma! Which button do I push?
どのボタン押すの？
（カヨ）え～っと…
Let's see...
（亮太）ねえってば！
C'mon, tell me!
Here, I think.
ここかな？
Yes, here. This button.
あっ ここだ　このボタン
（亮太）ここ？
Here?
Excuse me, I'm in a bit of a hurry...
（斉藤(さいとう)）
あの… ちょっと急いでるんですが
Excuse me, I'm in a bit of a hurry...
I'm sorry, we'll just be a little while longer.
すみません　もうちょっとですから
Yes, yes, Ryota, push here.
はいはい 亮太 ここ押して…
あっ 亮太 これ違うよ
Ryota, that's the wrong one!
もう１回
（亮太）え～ なんで？
Let's try again.
But why?
Allow me to press the button for you.
あの…
私 押して差し上げましょうか？
どちらまでです？
（カヨ）え～っと…
Where are you going?
Let's see, to Hinodedai.
日出台までなんですが…
（斉藤）
ああ… じゃ そこのボタンです
Oh, okay, then it's that button.
You are so kind.
ご親切に どうも
（斉藤）いえ
Don't mention it.
Oh my, nothing's coming out.
（カヨ）あら？ 出ないわね
（亮太）
おばあちゃん お金入れなきゃ
Grandma, you have to put in some money.
Oh, goodness gracious!
（カヨ）あら イヤだ
（男性）何やってる！ 早くしろよ
What are you doing?
Hurry up!
すみません　もう少しですから
I'm sorry, they'll only be a moment.
（男性）早くしろよ！
（春哉(はるや)）なあ 鉄ちゃん
So, Tetsu, I'm thinking of buying
a bigger one this time.
今度さ もっとでかいの
買おうと思ってるわけ
A motorcycle?
（鉄男(てつお)）単車か？
（春哉）あのさぁ…
Come on, when a biker says a bigger one,
he's talking about a motorcycle.
ゾクが“でかいの”っつったら
単車に決まってんだろう
（春哉）
大晦日(おおみそか)の八王子(はちおうじ)の走りまでに―
I wanna break in the engine before
the Hachioji race on New Year's Eve.
エンジン慣らしときたいんだよな
（鉄男）ふ～ん…
What? I'm serious!
（春哉）何だよ　マジだって！
I didn't say you were lying.
（鉄男）
ウソだなんて言ってねえだろう
Tetsu, lately you're starting to mellow out.
（春哉）鉄ちゃんさぁ 最近 丸いぜ
（鉄男）ああ？
（春哉）
ガキできると そんなもんかな
I guess that's what happens
when you end up having a kid.
ウッ… アッ… あちっ！
Hey, that's hot!
What the hell are you doing?
何すんだよ？
Shut up, fatass!
うるせえ このデブ！
丸くなんかねえ！
I am not mellowing out!
Haruya, don't you ever say that again!
春哉 二度と言うな！
（春哉）な… なに怒ってんだよ？
What are you all mad about?
Hey, Kosuke, did you know?
（欣二(きんじ)）おい 康介(こうすけ) 知ってる？
Tetsu's old lady's ain't loose with anything.
鉄ちゃんのカミさん
ケチくせえって
Yeah, Kinji. When you do it,
make sure you put on a rubber.
（康介）おう 欣二
ヤルとき ちゃんとゴムしとけや
ガキできると大変だぜ
It's no fun when you have a kid.
（笑い声）
（鉄男）…んだ こら！
You bastards! What's wrong with
a biker having a kid? Well?
てめえら ゾクがガキつくって
悪いんか！ ああ？
We didn't say that!
そ… そんなこと言ってねえべ
鉄ちゃん カッカすんなよ
Tetsu, don't get all pissed off!
（現場監督）
お～い 何やってる！ 休憩終わりだ
Hey!
What're you doin'?! Break time's over!
（康介・欣二）へ～い…
Yessir.
ハァ…
こ… こう？
（計）そう　それ！
Like this?
Yeah, like that.
アッ… そうやって着るんだ？
That's how you wear it.
（計）う～わ…
コスプレパブとか行くおっさんって
Wow, I bet guys who go to cosplay pubs
would get a kick out of this!
こういうの うれしいんだろうな
み… 見ないでよ
Don't look...
（計）い… いいか？ この間
岸本 それ着てなかったろう？
See, you weren't wearing that
the other day, right?
Yeah.
だけど それ かなり大事なんだ
But it's pretty important.
それ着てると 生き残る確率
ガーンて上がると思うんだよね
When you have it on, I believe your
chances of survival go way up.
So you've gotta practice.
だから 練習しないと
どうやって使うの？ これ
How do I use it?
Well...
え～っと…
（岸本）知ってるんでしょう？
You do know, right?
い… 言えねえ
I can't tell her that.
ねえ 玄野君 どうするの？
Hey, Kurono, how do you do it?
あの… とにかく
それ着て 気合い入れればいいんだ
Well... Anyhow, you just put it on
and give it your all.
I think. That's all.
…と思う　それだけ
はぁ？ だったら
わざわざ着替えなくても―
If that's all, couldn't you have just said that
without making me change clothes?
そう言うだけでいいんじゃないの？
そ… そうとも言うかな
You've got a point there.
Honestly!
もう！ 玄野君
ちょっと変態入ってるでしょう？
Kurono, you're kind of pervy!
No, I'm not!
そんなことないって…
学校行ってくる
I'm going to school.
えっ？ 行っちゃうの？
What? You're really going?
Yeah, I've got to.
だって 行かなきゃ
いいな…
（計）えっ 何が？
Must be nice.
What is?
とりあえず 学校行けて
At least you get to go to school.
行かなくていいんなら
そのほうがいいじゃん
If you don't have to go,
aren't you better off that way?
それ
行ける人だから そう思うんだよ
You only think that because you can go.
Hey...
あの…
（計）うん？
Can I meet you somewhere after school?
帰りに待ち合わせしていい？
ウッ… もしかして 今度こそ…
Maybe this time...
I want you to come along with me.
つきあってほしいんだ
All right! I'll go wherever you want!
（計）い… いいよ　どこへでも！
食事か？ 映画か？ それとも…
Dinner? A movie? Or...
私 もう１回 家へ行ってみたいの
I want to visit my house one more time.
もうひとりの自分が
どうしているか確かめたいの
I want to see how my other self is doing.
なんだよ
そういうことか… チェッ…
Oh, so that's what she wanted. Damn!
Is that too much trouble?
迷惑？
（計）あっ… 別に いいけど
No, it's all right.
ありがとう
Thanks.
West Fukasumi Titnipple High
（ヤンキーたち）ウッス…
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
（生徒）すみません　すみません
Don't mess with us, dork!
（ヤンキーＡ）
…ざけんなよ てめえ
What do we do with him?
（ヤンキーＢ）どうする？ こいつ
（ヤンキーＡ）
そうだ　とりあえず パンツ脱げ
I got it. Drop your pants.
I said, drop 'em!
（ヤンキーＡ）
脱げってんだよ ああ？
いや あの でも…
Well, but...
（ヤンキーＢ）
てめえ イライラすんなぁ
You're getting on my nerves, dork!
（生徒）
アッ… やめて！ やめてください！
Stop it! Please stop it! Stop!
やめて…
（せきばらい）
（ヤンキーたち）ああ？
（生徒）加藤君！
Kato!
Gee, you saved my life!
いやぁ 助かったよ
（加藤）そっか
That's good.
ビビったよ
マジで殺されるかと思ったよ
I was so scared. I really thought
they were gonna kill me.
行こっか　授業 始まるよ
Let's go. Class is gonna start.
We've gotta do somethin'
about that tenth grader.
（ヤンキーＢ）あいつ
なんとかしなきゃな あの１年
（ヤンキーＡ）ああ…
（ヤンキーＣ）どうする？
Yeah.
What should we do?
（ヤンキーＢ）今日？
（ヤンキーＡ）ああ 今日だろう
Today?
Yeah, today.
（ヤンキーＢ）
後ろからバットで頭殴って
みんなでボコボコにして…
Let's hit him in the head
from behind with a bat,
and then let everybody whale on him.
And we'll get rid of his clothes.
（ヤンキーＣ）服捨てちまってよ
Yeah. We'll get rid of his clothes.
（ヤンキーＡ）
そうだな　捨てちまって
（ヤンキーＢ）モップ突っ込むか？
（笑い声）
Let's shove a mop up his ass.
（鬼塚(おにづか)）そいつ 顔かわいいか？
Does he have a pretty face?
ウワッ… 鬼塚さん！
Onizuka!
（ヤンキーＢ）
なんで２年の便所入ってるんスか？
Why are you in the eleventh graders' john?
そいつ 俺にホラせろ
Let me give him a good butt-fucking.
Ever since the tenth grade,
this is the only place I come to shit.
（鬼塚）俺は１年のときから
ここでしかクソしねえんだよ
…で どんなヤツだ？ そいつ
So, what kind of guy is he?
なんか 変なヤツっすよ
He's a weirdo. He's always
hanging around with the wimps.
弱っちい生徒と
いっつも つるんでて
（鬼塚）弱いからじゃねえのか？
Isn't that because he's a wimp?
No, he's huge. I'd say he's about
one hundred ninety centimeters tall.
いや 見た目でけえし
190くらいあんじゃねえッスかね
When you try to threaten him, he gives you
this look that's as unforgiving as the devil.
（ヤンキーＢ）すごむと
目つき 鬼みてえに厳しいんスよ
俺がホる　いいな？
I'm gonna fuck him, got that?
（生徒）王手
Check!
あっ…
（生徒）エヘヘッ…
強(つえ)え！
（戸の開く音）
You're tough!
（ヤンキーＡ）おい 加藤
（加藤・生徒）うん？
Hey! Kato!
Masaru Kato! Come here!
（ヤンキーＡ）加藤勝(まさる) 来い
（加藤）何か用ッスか？
Is there something I can do for you?
（ヤンキーＡ）
今日 ３年と２年が組んで 大勢で
お前をリンチにかけるってさ
Today, a group of eleventh and twelfth graders
are going to gang up on you and beat you up.
A twelfth grade heavyweight pro boxer,
who happens to be a homo,
３年のヘビー級プロボクサーが…
そいつ ホモなんだけどな
お前のケツの穴 狙ってるぜ
is after your ass.
（生徒）
あっ 加藤君！ 大丈夫だった？
Kato!
Is everything all right?
ああ
（生徒）マジ？
Yeah.
You sure?
心配するなって！
将棋の続きやろうぜ
Don't worry about it.
Let's finish our game of shogi!
Philip the Second was assassinated,
and Alexander became the king.
（教師）
フィリッポス２世が暗殺され
アレキサンドロスが王位を継いだ
Turn to page thirty-four in your texts...
え～ 資料集の34ページを開いて
Furuta Books
Turn to page thirty-four in your texts...
I've told you over and over,
I hate women with large breasts.
（北条(ほうじょう)）何度も言ってんじゃん
俺 巨乳 嫌いなんだって
（女子学生Ａ）超美形じゃない？
What a dreamboat!
（女子学生Ｂ）
あれ？ 初めて見た？
What? You've never seen him before?
（女子学生Ｂ）
北条政信(まさのぶ)だよ　東世田谷(ひがしせたがや)高の
That's Masanobu Hojo,
from East Setagaya High.
Really? He looks like he could be a model.
（女子学生Ａ）
へえ… モデルとかできそうじゃん
（女子学生Ｂ）知らないの？
去年まで あの芸能事務所に―
Don't you know?
He was a member of that talent agency
up until last year.
入ってたんだってよ！
男の子ばっかの
The all-male one...
Seriously? Why'd he quit?
（女子学生Ａ）
マジだ？ なんで辞めちゃったの？
The president wanted to do him.
（女子学生Ｂ）
社長にヤラれそうになったんだって
（女子学生Ａ）
ふ～ん… そういうウワサ
やっぱホントなんだ？
So I guess those kinds of rumors
really are true.
Miranda Foster
Labyrinth
The bestseller now translated
and in paperback
"There is no labyrinth from
which you can't escape."
DAST Paperbacks
（聖(せい)）どうしたの？
（みか）えっ？
What's the matter?
たかが本でしょう？
そんなに驚かなくても
It's only a book. You don't have
to act so surprised.
（みか）あ… あの… ごめんなさい
I'm sorry.
I'm truly sorry. You can have the book.
（みか）本当に ごめんなさい
その本 どうぞ
（聖）別に
買おうと思ってるわけじゃないから
I wasn't really thinking of buying it, so take it.
どうぞ
（みか）いえいえ どうぞ…
No, you can keep it.
I said it's okay.
いいって
（みか）ど… どうも
Thanks.
顔色 悪いわ
（みか）そ… そうでしょうか？
You look pale.
Is that so?
もしかして ストーカーとか？
Could it be a stalker?
ハッ… どうして分かるんですか？
How do you know that?
Intuition, I guess. I'm rather sensitive
to those sorts of things.
勘かな
そういうの敏感なほうだから
でも いいんです
私の問題ですから
But it's okay. It's my problem.
Have you informed the police?
警察には知らせたの？
（みか）いいえ
No.
これ以上ひどくなったらとは
思ってるんですけど…
I'm thinking of doing that
if it gets any worse, but...
Oh, well, take care.
そう　気をつけてね
あ… ありがとうございます
あの… これ
Thank you. What about this?
遠慮しとく
I'll pass on it for now.
読みたい本は 読みたいときが
いちばん面白いもんよ
The books you want to read are more interesting
if you read them when you want to.
どうも…
Thanks.
（岸本）ごめん 待った？
（計）平気 平気
Sorry! Did you wait long?
It's okay.
（岸本）なに見てたの？
（計）い… いいから　行こっか
What were you looking at?
Never mind that, let's go.
What are you in such a hurry for?
I bet you were reading a dirty book.
（岸本）なに焦ってんの？
やらしい本でも読んでたんでしょう
（北条）
誰か バイク貸してくんねえ？
１万円やるから
Can someone let me borrow their bike?
I'll give you ten thousand yen.
（女子学生Ｂ）えっ？
（女子学生Ａ）あ… あの…
What?
Well, my boyfriend has a bike,
but what do you need it for?
私の彼氏
バイク持ってるけど なんで？
A lady stalker. She's always on my tail.
ストーカー女　超しつけえ…
俺の斜め後ろ　半分ぐらい出てる
She's behind me to your right.
About half of her is showing.
うわ 貞子(さだこ)みたい
（女子学生Ｂ）こわ～…
She looks like Sadako.
Scary.
あっ 彼氏に聞いてみるけどさ
その代わり 私 後ろに乗っていい？
I'll try asking my boyfriend, but in return,
can I sit behind you?
ち… ちょっと…
（北条）いいけど
Wait a sec!
That's okay. But I'm not
taking you home or anything.
送らねえよ 別に
（女子学生Ａ）ホント？
Really?!
Come here!
（店主）来い！
（万引き犯）いってえなぁ…
That hurts!
（万引き犯）離せって！
（店主）警察には連絡しないから
Let go of me!
I won't go to the authorities with this,
but in return, listen to what I have to say!
その代わり 私の話を少し聞け
お前な こんなこと
いつまでしているつもりだ？
Young man, just how long were you
planning on keeping this up?
Just for a little bit.
（女子学生Ａ）
お願い ちょっとだけだから
You gotta be kidding me!
（彼氏）…んだよ
（女子学生Ａ）いいじゃん
C'mon, please?
（ヤンキーＡ）おい！
（加藤）ああ？
Hey!
何だ？ こら
What the hell are you doing?
Masaru, it's my fault.
（歩）兄ちゃん 僕が悪いんだ
（加藤）“お前は既に死んでいる”
"You are already dead."
お前は既に死んでいる…
（加藤）アアーッ！
（鬼塚）分かった…
All right!
Stop!
（殴る音）
（鬼塚）やめてくれ… アアッ…
とにかく いいんだ
僕は平気だから
Anyway, it doesn't matter. I'm all right.
He's scary!
あいつ 怖え…
（生徒）ヘヘッ…
（加藤）アッ… 強えな お前
Man, you're tough!
（生徒）将棋だけは自信あんだ
The one thing I know I'm good at is shogi.
（ドアの開閉音）
（岸本）いってきます！
I'll be back!
う… うわ マジかよ
You've got to be kidding me!
（鉄男）ほ～ら 高い高～い！
（赤ん坊の笑い声）
Upsy-daisy, up you go!
タバコ買いに行ってくる
（妻）じゃ また牛乳
I'm going out to buy some cigarettes.
Okay, then get more milk.
（鉄男）ああ？ またか？
What? More?
The baby drinks a lot of it.
（妻）
この子 すんごい飲むんだもん
Unrivaled
Wicked Demon
The baby drinks a lot of it.
Unrivaled
Wicked Demon
Okay, why don't we take you
back to your mother?
さあ お母さんの所に帰ろうか
（亮太）うん！
Okay!
It's about that time. Maybe even tonight.
（西(にし)）そろそろ 今夜辺りかな
Well, shall we get down to business?
We all start out as pure and innocent babes
Even if you taste the bitter fruit,
don't be discouraged, walk straight
I know it's in the past, but the rain still stings
I'm lonely as floating ice
I kiss your thin finger
And remember you crying
Even if this is the end
I won't forget your last kiss
I won't forget
I won't forget his kiss
Many new people get drawn in,
and the game of death goes on forever.
（岸本）新たに何人もが巻き込まれ
死のゲームは永遠に続く
Will the newcomers be able to understand?
Can they survive?
新顔は理解できるのか？
生き残れるのか？
And if they can't, what should they do?
そうでない者たちは
何をなすべきなのか？
Next time: "Uh-oh!"
次回 “やベェ！”